Viewers all over the world, begin to command all spirits operating in your life,
operating in your health, tongue, hand, eyes and life - begin to command them out!
Right now, command them out!
All spirits operating in your life - command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Viewers, I can see the falling of satan in your life.
I can see the falling of failure!
I can see the falling of affliction!
I can see the falling of setback!
Career failure - I can see the falling!
I can see the falling of nightmare!
Right now, in the name of Jesus, agree with me:
Whatever satan might have used to connect you to himself - be broken, in the name of Jesus!
Be it failure - be broken, in the name of Jesus!
Be it affliction - be broken, in the name of Jesus!
Be it hatred - be broken, in the name of Jesus!
Be it nightmare - be broken, in the name of Jesus!
Pray, in the name of Jesus!
I can see chains have fallen.
Chains of affliction have fallen!
Chains of sickness have fallen!
Chains of failure have fallen!
In the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Give thanks to God!
TT: Lizz ndungu 27/10/2018
RV: Mel Flowers 04/11/2018